Petro Shepetko

Project Manager, Business Analyst

Portfolio: http://erp4b.pro Email: pshepetko@gmail.com



Summary

Expert in Information Technologies with 20+ years and more then 15 years in the ERP System implementation area; Excellent knowledge of the principles Enterprise Management. Lead Consultant in several large-scale projects:(1) Automation branch of state bank, (2) IT restructuring of bank, (3) ERP system for holding company, (4) ERP system for a transport company, (5) ERP system for steel mill. Project manager in several projects for implementation Open Source ERP system for Cable, Energy, Food, etc.; Good understanding of all modern technologies; Participation in the projects on the Poland and CIS countries: *Georgia, Kazakhstan, Russia, Uzbekistan and Ukraine.*

Experience

Freelance, self-employed.

03.2019 - Present

Implementation of the Opensource ERP system based iDempiere ERP Business Suite.

IT Systems Analyst "StabilisOne Ltd" company, Poland.

02.2018 - 02.2019

Localization and Implementation of the Opensource ERP system based *StabilisOne ERP Business Suite*.

Project Manager "U Palicha" company, Russia.

11.2013 – 10.2017 (3 years 11 months)

Implementation of the Opensource ERP system based *iDempiere ERP Business Suite*.

Project Manager in company FINA LTD, Ukraine.

03.2010 – 10.2013 (3 years 7 months)

Implementation of the Opensource ERP system based *iDempiere ERP Business Suite* on the CIS countries: *Georgia, Kazakhstan, Russia, Uzbekistan and Ukraine.*

Senior WMS consultant in Exorigo company (Oracle, Aldata partner in Poland), Kiev.

09.2008 – 02.2010 (1 year 6 months)

Implementation and Support WMS system based *Gold Stock 5.06* in Ukraine.

Senior ERP consultant in Infovide-Matrix company (Oracle partner in Poland), Kiev/Warsaw.

11.2007- 09.2008 (11 months)

Implementation of the ERP system based Oracle E-Business Suite in Poland.

Senior ERP consultant in Softline Business Practice company (Oracle partner in Ukraine), Kiev.

05.2006- 10.2007 (1 year 6 months)

Implementation of the ERP system based Oracle E-Business Suite in Ukraine.

IT manager in the Business Link company, Kiev.

09.2005 -04.2006 (8 months

Implementation Terrasoft CRM and Support the information structure of the company.

IT manager in the Stoic holding, Kiev.

05.2001-08.2005 (4 years 4 months)

Support the information structure of the holding (50 companies).

Programmer, Leading Expert on the introduction of 1C: Enterprise to LLC "Favorit-S", Kiev.

09.2000-05.2001 (9 months)

Implementation 1C: Enterprise system, including the development of its own configuration for the transport company.

Deputy Chief Accountant of the computerization of the State Treasury of Ukraine, Zhytomyr.

1997-09.2000 (3 years 7 months)

Supported software "Trading day of Treasury", developed and supported module "Payroll" (implemented in the 28 branches of region).

Head of Automation Department in Joint-Stock Commercial Bank "Ukraine", Ukraine.

1993-1997 (4 years)

Implemented a complex system of automation of bank branches; Software developed for reporting forms; Teached the staff working on the PC.

Projects

Open Source iDempiere ERP Business Suite

11.2013-10.2017

Members: Petro Shepetko

Implementation all modules of ERP system in the manufacturing enterprise.

Project Manager @ "U Palicha" company, Russia

03.2012-10.2012

Members: Petro Shepetko

Implementation modules: Purchasing, Inventory, Sales, Manufacturing, Accounting.

Lead Consultant/Developer @ "Textile factory", Uzbekistan

08.2011-12.2011

Members: Petro Shepetko

Implementation "Fixed Assets" module.

Lead Consultant/ Developer @ "Fixed Assets HH" company, Kazakhstan

Testimonials on-demand.

10.2009-09.2010

Members: Petro Shepetko

Implementation all modules of ERP system in the manufacturing enterprise.

Project Manager/Lead Consultant/ Developer @ "SAQCable" company, Georgia

Testimonials on-demand.

07.2008-03.2009

Members: Petro Shepetko

Implementation all modules of ERP system in the manufacturing enterprise and development

for GPS

module.

Project Manager/Lead Consultant/ Developer @ "NVOIT" company, Ukraine

Testimonials on-demand.

Oracle eBusiness Suite

11.2007-09.2008

Members: *Infovide-Matrix*

Implementation EAM module in the manufacturing enterprise.

Lead Consultant @ "ISD" company, Poland

05.2006-10.2007

Members: Softline Business Practice company

Implementation Fixed Assets, Cash Management, eAM and TMS modules.

Lead Consultant @ "FIM" company, Ukraine

05.2006- 10.2007

Members: Softline Business Practice company

Implementation Fixed Assets module.

Lead Consultant @ "PromTrans" company, Ukraine

Gold Stock 5.06 WMS

09.2008 - 02.2010

Members: Exorigo

Implemented WMS in the Warehouse for big Shops network in Ukraine.

Lead Consultant @ "Bukva" company, Ukraine

Languages

English Intermediate
Polish Intermediate

Ukrainian Native Russian Fluent

Education

1989-1995 Ukrainian academy of communication of O.S.Popov, Odessa

Speciality: Automation of technological processes

2004 Ukrainian Educational practical center of software engineering

Speciality: Software Project Management Professional

2007 Oracle University http://ilearning.oracle.com

Course aimed at modules: Fixed Assets, Cash Management, EAM, TMS

2018 edX/LinuxFoundationX http://edx.org

Blockchain for Business Professional Certificate

2020 InLingua School of Languages, Malta

IELTS Exam Preparation course (8 weeks), level C1.

Link: https://www.linkedin.com/in/pshepetko/

